Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Intel Extreme Masters Taipei Day 1.
You thought you were going to have to wait another 9 minutes.
Well guess what?
The admin was wrong.
The players were ready faster than they said they would be.
Look at that.
We are already loading in to the first map of the next series.
It's PVP Jeff.
There's no more Terrence tonight, which means I can freely be biased without anyone judging
me.
Of course.
That's still not possible.
You will, of course, be judged.
Really excited to match SOS, of course, the Blizzcon Champion.
Yeah.
One of the guys that I felt like had perhaps the best year last year.
And it's certainly in the discussion if you don't agree with that, versus Mintchol, who
is historically one of the biggest earners and biggest names in all of Starcraft, kind
of a godfather to a lot of players and just a special awesome guy.
So what a treat to be able to cast this match and be here at this stage.
Really awesome to see both of these players here.
Yeah.
Very interested to see how these guys play some legacy of the Void PVP in the top right
of course.
We have MC.
And if you look at his Twitter, the streamer MC, he's been streaming.
He actually, I think he's done two runs now where he's gone to top 16, Jim and Kriya.
He's got like his next streamed crazy plans.
I'm going to get number one.
He's a hard worker.
Cool, dude.
And of course, in the bottom left, we have SOS.
Oli is still with generic green wings.
You said let's call champion.
One of the most difficult opponents you could possibly face, he has very finely tuned
builds.
This is not necessarily a super free style player like, well, he does get into free style
mode, but for the most part, he goes into each game.
I think in a, I believe I can credit Rotterdam with his comment as saying that he feels
like he has kind of a pre-plan build and plays around that.
And I feel like that's pretty aptly true.
And you can see he's actually fully walled in, gets the probe out.
He's going to scout around.
So this is of course geared towards preventing adips from doing any damage at all.
Of course, they do very little damage to buildings and it's not likely that they're
going to hammer through that.
But again, just talking about both of these guys.
I mean, I'm showing away from saying he's earned the most, but I think he might be the
highest earner in Starcraft 2.
But if not top 5, top 3, I think he's there.
I was just looking at it recently.
Big big deal.
He did say he's kind of giving up pro gaming, going into streaming.
But what's kind of cool about a lot of these guys is sometimes when you take the pressure
off the shoulders and they're able to kind of play it their own way, sometimes it's
usually the consistency that falls off, but you'll see them peak and do fairly well.
I think Stefano's another player you can kind of look back to who had a moment of time
there where he's like, I'm not playing as much.
I barely practice with this term and then you go and crush it and do really well.
And we've seen, of course, that's not the norm.
It's not normal to be like, I'm going to take Starcraft less serious and then everyone
does better.
But some guys, MC being up there, they can do it.
Yeah.
It's definitely not something for everyone to do.
No, practice is a certainly very important part of being a professional gamer.
But MC moving out.
So you already pointed out that he's got the solid set up here with that added blocking
wall as it were.
It's got to be true about on the map anyway.
This is interesting.
We're actually not seeing a tech path out of mental just yet, MC.
Which is kind of focusing.
He is going to have the adept out there.
But SOS, if he's known for anything by the way, it is absolutely his dark Templar play.
He is, it's like kind of comical.
A lot of people are like, it's ridiculous how many times you'll see dark Templar.
But hey, man, if it ain't broke, don't fix it.
And dark Templar in all three matchups will win you games.
Absolutely.
Just off the RNG of whatever build they're doing.
But this is going to be a proxy robot, which actually in a lot of ways, Nate, can be
bad.
Look at how fast that dark shrines.
It's about to finish.
And the observers can be built from across the map.
Yeah.
And at the same time, SOS, he gets that adept into the natural of MC, Hicks off Probe gets
to scout a little bit.
A shade not seen anything particular.
So maybe he's concerned.
He's like, well, what are you cheesy me with?
He's got his own robot on the way.
Once you said it, the dark shrines about to finish.
He's got a pile on.
But it's a little bit ill timed if we're going to be pretty critical of ourselves.
Really, this is a pile on and also a gateway.
Of course, it will end up just being a pile on in the dark Templar.
It's going to take 16 seconds to warp in.
But whatever.
It's going to take him so long.
Yeah.
And this should be game ending.
No, like he should be over right here.
It is, unfortunately.
MC is going to, well, it is.
He proxy robot against a dark Templar rush.
What's going to happen is MC is going to have a sizable force over here anchored by
at least an immortal, maybe two.
And he's going to have the ability to make an observer.
So it could be a base trade situation.
But I feel like it would be really incredible if, if SOS didn't have enough at home, at least
slow down that attack and make it so that it is not enough.
And this is just brutal right now.
The DT is getting in, slicing and dice in every probe.
There's not much you can do.
He's going to make that attack.
Like you said, this is the big moment.
So he's going to pick off that pile on.
Somebody pulls back and I feel like he's got enough enough to overcharge another pile on
as well.
He's just going to keep Warp Reinsenters.
It's over.
I understand MC's angle.
He's like, well, I've got to play this real safe because if I lose this force, I'm dead.
But unfortunately for him, it was always about just killing.
You need to kill that pile on.
And the one other pile on immediately.
And that was his only chance.
His only shot in hell.
But unfortunately, that's not panning out.
He's losing all his probes.
I mean, MC's army manages to get inside of SOS's base.
He's going to pull the probes here.
And at this point, I guess he doesn't, he just had his own observer.
I mean, if you got MC's observer, then you could just weapon DTs.
But he's got two observers here now.
Part of the toss.
Pound off, but it's on a mortal, right?
So this should be basically it.
He's done.
He's done it.
He's unpowered the gauge.
GG.
SOS takes the first map.
I mean, it's just a little bit of you has to not necessarily roll your eyes, but shake
your head and be like, how does SOS keep winning games?
It's like he can't keep getting away like this.
It's like, like, you know, Poltmerrotters.
You know he's going to split up his army in TVZ.
You're not going to be prepared for that.
TVP as well.
So you kind of, you should formulate that into your, this is how I'm going to handle him
with SOS.
He of course doesn't only do DTs, but like I would be interested to say, let's look at
last 10 SOS games.
How many of those games of DTs appear in?
I would say six or seven of the 10 and how many of those were like DT openings?
Probably four or five followed by a DT opening.
If it wasn't a DT opening, like he's very, very fixated on dark temple.
Or to lose to that is a little, I mean, of course the game is not that simple.
It's not like he goes DT.
He did.
He does.
And I went.
He did go for like a really fast DT though as well.
Before either player got any real tech, right?
You usually get the mothership core.
MC went mother ship core before his proxy robo, but I mean, SOS cut everything possible
to get that out as fast as he could.
And it was a bit slow of a robo, which is interesting.
Speaking of free styling players, MC is a guy that will freestyle in a matchup.
He'll be like, he won't necessarily say, I know what first map is and this is the
bill I'm going to do.
He'll go into it and have like a couple of builds in mind.
So I'm not saying that's why the robo is delayed, but that could be a part of it.
To proxy a robo like that against SOS, I'm not sure what build you're hoping for as I guess
my point.
Super fast blink finishes by then.
Blink would have been okay there.
Any Stargate play is problematic in a lot of ways.
So it is kind of just a weird strategy to go for.
Yeah, really.
It was map number two ruins of Saras.
We are loaded in currently leading one.
Oh, SOS in the bottom right.
Nice, nice spot to start the series off on getting that quick cheeky win.
Of course, I'm like, see the void the game ramps up so fast.
It also ends the haunting win too that going mega fast, DT like that is going to be in the
back of MC's mind for the rest of the series.
Yeah.
And I mean, I guess it's one of those things where it's like you're up against SOS so
you're like, well, I should have this in the back of my mind, but maybe well, then you
know, then we go back to your logic, which is when he knows that I should expect it so
he won't do it.
And then he, you know, you could just go back and forth and that forever.
Yeah.
He knows that I'll think that he knows that I know.
It's just a great opening build though because even if it doesn't work out in a best of
five, it still sends information to your opponent.
So it kind of factors into what builds they want to do it.
It makes them feel a little bit more risky about perhaps doing the same build.
And it just kind of works in your favor both ways.
Like obviously getting the win is the ultimate goal, but even if you don't win, that kind
of opening kind of throws your opponent off.
Like if you just open up Nexus first or Gateway Nexus followed by Robo, like very safe,
very studious, that also sends, I mean, this is Starcraft.
There's like so many messages you're sending, of course, but in my point is it sends
a much more tepid message.
Like I'm going to receive you and it gives you kind of a more confident feeling about
doing radical.
So tell me about this opening a little bit where you have double gateway with the cyber
net explorer.
Definitely not as economic as this because they can't block the natural law with the
highlands like it in the last map or what?
Yeah, you're exactly right.
And the idea here, of course, is going to be an adaptor to hoping to do quite a bit
of damage at the mineral line.
But as you said, the nice thing about that is a lot of times if you couldn't do that
damage, well, you were dead because they have that expansion and they're just so far ahead.
But on this map, walling off that natural is really not a realistic thing you can do.
And again, because of photon overcharge being a little bit more expensive, it's also not
like you can just absolutely annihilate and shut down adips.
All of a sudden takes several photon overcharge that you don't have anymore.
So just a very solid opening.
So SOS is going to open with double stalker, like that mothership core coming out faster
for MC.
They're both going double stalker.
So is this meant to counter the adiped play or it's met opening and it's in its no balls.
So like let's say the guy does go two adips and expands behind that and then does some kind
of text, stargate or robo.
Well, if you show up with six stalkers and a single pile on is not going to hold it off
and you can't actually kill those adips in enough time that all of a sudden their opening
is is is thwarted.
They don't have any force to defend against you and you're not punishing them.
So he canceled.
He canceled.
Oh no, if you finish.
He's not building anymore.
Okay.
I didn't see the stalkers come out.
I was I was almost panicking for a second.
It happens to the best of us.
But MC is actually cronobosing his warp gate upgrade.
It is.
So it's doing the same.
We can go into the base.
They're very close for both players.
They both are so pretty much exactly the same build so far.
Yeah, very so why go down to this is come down to micro, right?
And it looks like the shields are being traded evenly on both sockers.
First, real damage being taken.
You cast this.
I mean, well, no, I mean, it's just.
Oh, watching two beautiful players a little bit of a slight miss there.
First blood for us.
So next next is down at the exact same time as well, which is actually kind of a scary
nexus because both these players and two now that is interesting.
Centuries.
But why'd ramp like that?
Like, obviously, you want at least one century fairly early on, not for defensive capabilities,
but because you want to throw a hallucination, you'll notice both these builds don't have
a robo.
They don't have a target.
There's the robo at the exact same time.
But that's quite a bit of a late robo.
Neither of these players know what their opponents doing, but because their stalkers dueled
in the middle of the map, because the probe did scout in there and they kind of saw not
an immediate attack there.
They're basically going off intuition and instinct.
This is probably one of the more dominant.
Dominant.
As far as common builds on the Korean server in particular amongst the top players, the
difference here is we do see that MC is going for a fast Twilight council, but also the
two centuries, which I think is really interesting.
Yeah.
They can't force Bill to ramp.
You said it already with being able to throw its hallucination to scout later on, but
yeah, force field is definitely not that must be used.
Yeah, it's a little bit curious.
And actually, if we can get a look at MC's base real quick, I would say that Pilot
the natural if we could.
No, so it's not even on the ramp.
So I just flat out don't understand.
And so I was gonna push in here the centuries
in the back, tagging a little bit,
but I guess that lag of high ground vision,
he takes that first shot and he's just gonna step off.
Yep, as Blink starts up, Fremsy,
and where will he see?
And Immortal coming out from SOS.
He cancel goes for the observer,
a little bit concerned that he's gonna get a retaliatory,
and he has three centuries.
So yeah, I'm excited to see where this goes.
He just takes a third base,
and that's a very fast third base.
And just now is adding his own Twilight Council.
So he will of course, tech the Blink as well.
Immortals by the way are an interesting spot in PvP,
because disruptors make them pretty much useless,
but that's a stage away, but not too far away.
So it's kind of a stalker's dominate the early
to mid game part of PvP in most standard games.
So that's where the Immortal's really shine,
but they immediately become quite bad
when disruptors come out.
A lot of players are trying to,
like they're feeling out their comfort zone of like,
okay, well I'm gonna skip Immortals,
go really fast disruptors, which is quite bad
against super mass bling stalkers,
but if I can get to the disruptor bling stalker stage,
now I'm advantage, whereas the other guy was slowed down
by having a lot of bling stalkers, but then making Immortals.
So it's kind of an uncomfortable give and take,
and perhaps that's why we're seeing several centuries.
Of course, it's not necessarily for the Force Shield.
It's to be on top of, are you going disruptors,
are the two of us gonna have an arm's race of Immortals?
It's a, the disruptors are really such a volatile thing
to throw into a matchup like PvP,
where the unit count is pretty much always what's determined
to win, whereas now it's more like,
can you get into a good position versus the disruptors?
And you know, there's also like that,
that kind of like kind of, I don't know,
gamble you can make with bling stalkers and disruptors,
like if you wanna blink in and try to snipe a disruptor
while you're throwing yours, et cetera, et cetera.
There's such a, I love the little up dynamics added by that,
but without a robo-based rather side,
it's just Immortals and stalkers versus Immortals and stalkers.
And if you just go on for it by,
if we're gonna get, we was about to finish it
behind this award-prison coming out.
He's already pushing across the map,
the Ford forces of S-O-S did spot the South,
so he's coming back to, kind of defend,
but almost certain that third base becomes a bit of a liability,
especially if he wants to defend out on the map,
but if MC pushes too early and loses too many of his forces,
he will just die because this third base is the,
it's the gambit, so to speak,
it's, it's winning or losing choice.
It's what he's made this, made the plays in this game.
Oh, it's already here.
It's early on, and now the army is,
here's gonna overcharge one pylon,
as he starts the warp ends by that nexus,
getting a little bit of damage down here.
He's gonna force field in some of the centers
in the Immortals, trying to make a play here.
He does have one of the Immortals locked in
as it triggers that barrier ability of it.
And now, without a mortal going down,
S-O-S has the Immortal lead.
Can he defend this base, though, Jeff?
Warpers in here is gonna allow him to warp in.
Actually, if he kills that pylon,
there'll be no warp in on this location,
and I think he's actually waiting for the trial warp in,
which is pretty cool.
S-O-S already on top of that decision
by warping in over it as natural,
which is the further away choice.
But the safer one, MC micro me back,
beautifully, the two morals, as you said,
they're dealing out so much damage.
One of the moral is about to die,
and it does good concave for MCMC,
is down in supply overall,
but I think part of that is actually harvesters,
linking back, but there's just,
and now the flotch and overcharge,
he does have to pick off that pylon,
and he does that.
That being said, though.
That being said, though, really important as well.
So, he does make sure that despite all of this,
or both on two bases,
and he continue to warp and try to plight more of the pressure
in this instance of the warping.
S-O-S had a comparable army, oh my god,
two of morals joined this by the way,
becoming much more powerful.
And she's gonna be just happy with this little wind
and pull back, but S-O-S says,
you know what, with you picking off the Nexus,
why am I fighting here?
He pulls back, he might have had a slightly stronger army
before those two of morals joined,
but with the two of morals,
he certainly has the stronger army.
Yep, so he just pulls back knowing,
he doesn't need to fight in that location.
Oh, Link's back.
I'm going forward trying to get the Immortals.
Does not manage to...
Oh my god, but it's such a crazy choice
because there's Blink Sockers right there as well.
So that Blink is gonna cost him.
These Sockers are chasing him down
and there's just not enough space for MC Sockers
to get too far away,
because if they go in on those blue Sockers of S-O-S,
they're gonna face three Immortals,
which will dice him up in no time at all.
So MC takes a crazy choice.
He's waiting for this violence to finish.
He's gonna have a lot of photon overcharge.
A huge century warp in back at home again for S-O-S.
I love your guys' comments.
I mean, I don't pretend to know everything,
but that is very curious.
He has a lot of gas and low on minerals.
That's what he's doing, I guess, but...
Hmm, interesting.
He said in the market across the map.
He has a dark shrine on the way as well with the Warp Rism.
So opening up the door for some harass-based play
without having to do the direct assault,
but if you can distract him long enough,
I mean, could do quite a bit of damage.
He's getting highlands on here as well.
Yeah, he's taking his third behind this.
So it's not like this is an all-in of any sort.
And the little time that he did have
with that third nexus method,
he's doing pretty good on harvishes.
He's actually only up three, which is interesting.
So a lot of this is army supply.
And here come centuries,
they're gonna try to capture these Immortals.
So that is what they're gonna do.
Picking off one very cost effectively.
And those stock around the wrong side of those forest fields.
So my question's answered,
they're just for positional battle.
It's beautiful to see again.
I guess the part of the reason why I have a tough time
with them is because again,
disruptors are second to come out.
They'll just become completely useless.
MC also has no observers on the map.
So as the Stark Shrine finishes up,
it's also highly possible that the addition
of Dark Temple I really heard him quite a bit.
He's warping in his first one.
Finally, another observer starts up, but.
Oh, it's something to be worried about.
It's not a gateway to highlands.
It's gonna take a while.
I love this observer by the way from MC.
That's like so MC.
Just has a good intuition about him.
He's like, you know what?
I'm noticing an observer above my army.
I don't have the text.
I should get an observer
and it's gonna come out in just the right time.
That being said,
though, his warperism is in the base.
MC senses it.
He kind of,
maybe he learned his lesson from that first game.
I can only drop one in.
He wants to test the water.
See what's there.
Three DTs can do a lot,
but let the observer now being out.
It's possible things get tricky,
but he could be as he's trying to force a big warping
in home and then maybe make his push
or force him to blink some units back inside of his main base.
And then attack.
He is peeling off a few stalkers,
so to get that DT.
Is he gonna,
is that so it's gonna force it now?
That's a big question.
Now the DT goes in a third.
Like MC was caught in a tough spot.
One observer is just simply not enough.
He's actually making him mortals off the robot, by the way,
just settling for the one, the one observer.
And he's losing everything.
The most important is on the edge of its life.
Maybe not gonna die necessarily,
but these force fields are beautiful.
We're seeing the living action
of why these guys chose to warp in as many centuries as they did.
15 probes dying at all three next side.
Behind us,
I think the main was closed up,
but I mean,
at what cost Nathanius,
the age-old question.
He had to buy it at a high price, I would say, controlled.
He's been taking a beating,
and that warperism is still lurking about outside of his base.
We have the Robo Bay coming in for us,
I think, in this position,
and he starts to get to structures here
then he can make anything he wants.
Yeah.
He's in such a good spot.
Struppers, of course,
the good-looking choice here.
And all force fields in another immortal pixel.
I'm loving it.
I was really wondering what these guys were about,
but both these players knew it was going to come down
to Blinkstalker Micro-Incred by Immortals,
and that's where the centuries really shine.
That was really nice being able to pinch those forces in.
Another DT getting warped inside of the main base,
another one aimed at the natural expansion,
and he's just picking MC apart.
MC can't handle it.
There's just too much pressure.
G-G-S-O-S takes the second map in this best of five.
And to give credit,
what credits do?
So a lot of people saw with that Robo,
MC just kept making Immortals,
and then the back of all of our minds probably,
was us being very critical of that.
Why are you doing that?
You're getting picked apart by DTs.
I think MC made that really tough Starcraft choice,
where he's like, okay, well, if I make any more observers,
yeah, stop the DTs,
but I will die to the Army overall.
I need to keep making Immortals,
hope to pick off the Warp Prism,
hope SOS backs off in the idea of DT harassing,
but SOS being so savvy,
seeing that even over top the third,
there was no observer,
probably did the math in his head,
and said there's one, maybe two out here.
Dark Temple are going to get their money's worth,
and if not, I'm gonna have the better Army
because he made more observers.
So it just really cool back and forth
by the two players,
hard choices are made in Starcraft.
We can be critical of MC for that,
but I think in this situation,
he just knew he had to go with what he thought
was lesser of the evils.
Yep, next map is gonna be Orbital Shipyard,
and it's such a tough spot when you're in that position
because the observer obviously can't be in both bases at once,
and I really like that you pointed out that,
even with the Army in his face,
he's like, yep, I'm gonna send a DTA to the base, right?
Next year Army,
because you already moved your observer to the main,
you're gonna have to move it to the natural next,
and you touched on something that was really cool too,
that the choice to send one DT is very savvy and cool.
He had three, so he could have dropped all three DTs,
sent him into the main,
and been like, you're dead,
I'm gonna maybe pick off the robo,
kill everything into the game,
but if there is an observer in there,
if MC is on top of that,
has several observers,
that all of a sudden those three DTs
became a really big cost,
and it's really, we've seen Prodoss flip their advantage
on their head because they spend too much on that,
but just beautiful playful players.
DTs, very expensive,
but got a lot of value out of them so far in this best of five,
this blue Prodoss on the top right, SOS, okay?
I believe you said it earlier,
I was like, yeah, okay, DTs, okay?
But I think anyone in the chat
who disagrees with UJF has been proved fooled.
Well, they all know it.
You know, SOS loves DTs.
If he doesn't open with them,
it's like the fall back to everything,
Stargate, okay, well, DTs are next.
Robo, okay, fine, but DTs are next.
DTs, sure, but then...
DTs are next.
Yeah, that's it.
That's a fun way to play Stargate.
Because you know, usually like the dark temple are playing
or at least like in other matchups comes in,
it's either it's the focus of your play
with either like a rush, or it's,
I probably can't win this game anymore.
Let's just make DTs and just, you know, hope,
hope for the best.
Sometimes it works, sometimes you just lose.
Yeah, I mean, depending on what you do,
if you do the opening of DT,
like we saw in game number one,
and MC's just sitting there with an observer,
just great, it's tough.
Because if you do, if you are that guy,
like me that sends in three DTs,
so they're like, I need to win right now,
then it can be your dead.
But what I like about SOS so much is that even when it appears
to be in all-in, it kind of isn't.
It's kind of like, yeah, okay, you killed that first DT.
It's like, I can still work with this,
but leave your army at home, make cannons.
Because if you don't, the DTs will come back
and they will get their costs one way or another.
They're gonna get their pound of money.
He's very good at utilizing them in this matchup,
it seems.
SOS with the block off against, nope, not coming inside
and similarly, we have MC.
MC will make a robo or a stargate, like 1,000%.
He is like Pavlov's dog in train right now
that when he sees a closed off like that,
against maybe any other pro-dots,
he'd be like, no way would they go dark temple art again.
This is to trick me, but against SOS,
he's like, he thinks I'll think that he's not going DTs,
but I know he's going DTs, so he'll be red.
Yeah, and it's still this setup with two gateways though,
from MC, so is he looking to just apply direct pressure?
I mean, this probe is actually,
he's got to be careful though.
He's taking the shields off this pile on.
Yeah, he's going to pull back.
Oh my goodness.
It's his only probe.
So now what he's saying is if this is your only
stalker coming out, my mother's of course
is going to actually make it across the map
and I'm going to have stalkers there too.
So if this is the only gateway, you're in trouble.
And it is the only gateway.
He doesn't have any of the production.
He's going to start up another one.
And I guess what, you just kill the, what's the focus here?
I break the pile and get inside, kill the core,
where do you go with this?
Nice, this game weird.
Yeah, I mean, at best he does break it in there.
You're going to see a photon overcharge in a second
because SOS is panicking.
He doesn't know how close his most of course.
He needs to kill that pile right now.
He will kill that pile on, but that photon overcharge
is his only one for now.
Yeah, it's nice that way.
Oh, he did wait.
It's nice that he was patient with it
because he has it now for when these stalkers
are really in a flat need to be patient.
They're still, you know, there's more pylons.
There's at least one full health pylon
he'll be able to use and there's the first overcharge.
He's about to have 12 seconds away from his next one.
There's the overcharge.
Pick up the most.
Does pick up the most of core.
Nice grab.
You know, immediately be building it.
It'll actually spawn with enough energy to overcharge.
You can't.
Yeah, that's the upside there.
It's like the only good thing about losing your mother
ship course is that it actually just gets energy faster
than we important real time.
Now keep in mind, this warp gate upgrade is now
actually powered by one pylon.
He is going, yeah, that's true.
He is going to build two gateways outside of his opponent's
fate and another pylon.
OK, so it is getting super weird.
MC is putting it all in here, boys.
His own warp gate is finished.
So he's going to be able to warp in here in a second.
Weird is the only way I can describe this.
So I love it.
It's nice to be able to get warp gate.
That's for sure.
I'm losing that would have caused me deem losing here.
It's one of the best ways to deal with someone that's a lot.
Oh, and the stock actually warps in on the heart.
Comes out on the wrong side.
But there's no overcharge.
He has a stock account lead.
If all the stockers are shooting at once, which they are,
this should be favorable for us, so I know.
I mean, it worked out OK because of the reason you just
stayed with him.
But he would have, he would have ideally preferred it.
Sorry.
I don't know.
So Mother's ship corps finally close to getting
another overcharge.
She's got two warp gates.
He's literally outside of his base.
I mean, there you go.
You can't do that pylon.
MC.
That is.
MC is aggressive.
Desperation coming out of MC here.
That was a bit aggressive.
I mean, no natural.
I think he canceled that to go against the first before he
was too, which gives him a spotting.
So it's a bit very...
There's a century.
So he's going to be able to pick off a couple extra stalkers
who are locking him in.
And he has that overcharge available as well.
And these stalkers are both going to die.
Yeah.
Couple of very sloppy choices to lose the probe to that kind
of a pylon, very curious, going up the ramp at all
without being able to spot high ground
because he lost the Mother's ship corps.
And SOS has an immortal on the way, too.
So that's going to be the get out of this game of mortal.
And now, by the way, all of a sudden, going up this ramp
is like the scariest thing on planet Earth each time.
Because the centuries, he's got another century.
And then the photon overcharge.
And this is bad.
Bye-bye.
Just making zealots the same as him in here as well.
Yep.
He's moving in now as well.
The zealots are here at the top of the ramp
trying to help push this back.
There's that force field overcharge enabled.
And bye-bye stalkers.
It's like this phenomenal defense from SOS.
It's beautiful.
Really cool use of the adip, actually.
He let it finish.
So it ends up being bad.
But how do you just use the shade to spot high ground?
He can actually always cancel that and the cooldowns
so short that you're basically able to see up there for free.
But again, MC kind of missx.
And shout out to these guys for keeping all the action
in one spot.
It's a pretty much easier to observe.
Yes.
I mean, subtle things are being done in the background.
Robo's ratted, but now Immortal's coming out.
Yeah.
Immortal, right?
So breaking this, no upgrades, no real tech.
It's not possible.
And consider that there's two mineral lines available for SOS.
If these guys just traded even forever and ever,
that main's going to mine out.
And MC will be long distance mining
is natural before we see anything else happen.
No, I super all in.
No natural for him.
Yeah, you just gave us a shot of SOS's natural.
I was like, oh, he's not really satry there.
But he doesn't have any satry.
Yeah.
So it's a bold play.
Hey, here.
I MC, but it doesn't seem to have paid off.
I mean, SOS is just in such a good spot.
Atoms did get into the natural.
So he gets a few progs here.
It's something.
But it ain't much.
What MC needs now is for SOS to make this incredibly weird choice.
To just move down his ramp from the horizon.
And he gets force to fill it off, yeah.
But now he has an observer.
He sees everything.
He could even probably make the decision
to throw a hallucination to MC and just confirm.
Just be like, oh, can you have it expanded?
So I actually just sit here making centuries and immortals.
Yeah.
He's trying to do the PVT thing, right?
I'm just using these adips to try to distract by time,
bring himself back into this game.
But there's no coming back into this game
by killing progs when you're still on one base.
All right.
He's just doing what he can.
I mean, each warp in is so important too.
These adips are going to kill maybe a pro or two.
But in doing so, they are also warpins that MC desperately
needed to have any chance.
But I say that as the super-optimistic caster, again,
SOS has an observer looking at MC's army.
And he's just a good enough player to be like,
this is all you have.
You do not have anyone.
Yeah.
I mean, SOS just needs to keep holding on.
Slowly build up more.
And I guess, what do you get to end this game?
DT's, I'm going to cross the map.
He's going to step up the ramp.
He gets force fielded in, mortal.
Here comes the attack, the ramp.
He's going to try, gets the immortal.
And a lot of the teeth has been taken out.
But keep in mind, a lot of it's actually inside the main of SOS,
trying to figure out if that's the more important defense or not.
But he has so many force fields.
So here we go.
Yeah.
Now that he's finally catching these stalkers
on the ramp, and they're pushing over,
trying to get dropped.
The model comes back.
GG's called SOS.
With a 3-0 here.
Pretty cool games.
2-0 did end with DT.
So it's very like.
And you know what?
He had a twilight on the way there.
So I'm just going to say he's going for DT.
That's what I mean.
When you've got an observer on top of your opponent,
it's on me for that long.
He's like, he just doesn't have a robo or anything.
Does he?
And any text or it's just a funny part.
And some dark templar showed up in your mineral lab.
Could have been dark templar.
He could have made a stargate.
An oracle would have been game ending.
He could have made a robotic stage.
And he could have been a, I mean,
if you really wanted to, he could have made a prison as well.
He had the robo, right?
So.
But a cool, again, I like that MC.
MC's that guy who 02 against SOS is like,
I'm going to start dropping pylons.
I'm going to add gateways to this.
And I'm going to go for it.
And it seems really weird and bad.
But with his micro and his, for black of a better word,
kind of his balls, like he just will do crazy stuff like that.
So where did it go wrong, then?
What was the biggest thing in that last game that just
dropped in the mothership core?
Losing the mothership core, I think,
is the beginning of the end for him not
being able to spot the high ground with a mostly
stalker force becomes, it just gets completely flipped
on its head.
It goes from being kind of scary.
And maybe with a couple of good volleys, you pick off
the high ground pylons.
You start picking off the centuries.
2, I got nothing.
And that's what cost him.
Then he goes up the ramp kind of loses two stalkers
in his elbow, I think, for free, essentially.
So that was the end of it.
All right, well, very well played by SOS
as he advances on here at the Intel Extreme Master's Taipei.
He will be playing tomorrow in day two
against the winner of our last series of the night.
We've got snoot versus hero coming up.
An interesting match.
I'm very interested to see this mostly
because the patch has made like PDZ win rates
are pretty bad in terms of products.
Products been losing a lot versus or recently.
So this patch, most products have been pretty upset
with the result in terms of dealing
with early Zerg aggression.
So, but I mean, you also have a hero on this pedestal.
Yes.
As well.
And you're like, snoot's good, but is he hero good?
Like, I don't really think so.
He's hero wins, IEMs.
That's what the guy does.
So.
Yeah.
It'll be interesting.
And snoot, of course, is that guy that
has been the household foreigner name
for going on three years now.
We just always has been one of the absolute best foreigners.
And here he is again, in a situation
where I think the meta-faced favors him.
And again, you can call me a salty product.
So I want, but I do think Zerg's quite strong right now.
I'm a tan and I'm on your side with.
I watched a reasonable amount of ZBP since that patch.
And it's rough.
I'm very intrigued in a non-caster way
as to how hero is going to play this.
And if snoot is going to be able to use something
with that patch to edge out, you know, because I mean,
he's not, he's shown before he's not
afraid to go for the abuse of salt.
We're going to bring you that best of five
after this next commercial break.
Be about to see your seven minutes.
We'll see you guys in just a little bit.